Guide to the Riot Grrrl zine and music collection, circa 1989-1997.
Riot Grrrl zine and music collection,
- Sound and Video Recordings, 1991-2000
  - Cassettes, 1991-2000
    - What Doctors Don't Tell You, 1993; TR-15932; God Is My Co-Pilot; Shrimper (Box 9)
      SHR 46
      Upland, California
    - Heavenly Vs. Satan, 1991; TR-15933; Heavenly; Sarah Records (Box 9)
      SARAH603 | TUEK9102
      France
    - Heavens to Betsy, 1992-02-29; TR-15934 (Box 9)
    - Julep - Another Yoyo Studio Compilation, 1993; TR-15935; Kreviss; Bratmobile; Crayon; Slowpoke; Lync; Long Hind Legs; Rockin Rod and the Strychnines; Fruit Bat; Adickdid; Young Ginns; Heavens to Betsy; Cub; Kicking Giant; Karp; Tattle Tale; Nikki and Rachael; Slant 6; Chorea; Tiger Trap; Yoyo Recordings (Box 9)
      YOYO CS-2
    - Boyfriend Girlfriend, 1990; TR-15936; Kicking Giant; Loose Leaf (Box 9)
      Loose Leaf #2
    - Halo, 1993; TR-15937; Kicking Giant; Loose Leaf (Box 9)
      Loose Leaf Project No. 5
    - Present, 1992; TR-15938; Kicking Giant; Loose Leaf (Box 10)
    - Secret Teenage Summer, 1991; TR-15939; Kicking Giant; Loose Leaf (Box 10)
      Loose Leaf Project No. 3
    - All Dolled Up, 1996; TR-15940; Lookers, The (Box 10)
    - Fortunes from The F-Holes, 1996; TR-15941; Madigan (Box 10)
      West Hollywood, California
    - The Need, 1995-12; TR-15942 (Box 10)
    - Quean Scream, 1997; TR-15943; Nosotrash; Athena Starwoman; No. 12 Looks Just Like You; Hello Kitty; Yucky Charms; Catcall; harry Carry; Foxfires; Instant Hits, The; Sinister Cherry; Shimmy Beckers, The; Pristines, The; Linda; Fusselman, Amy; Dead Kitty; Yum-Yum Tree; La Mera Mera; Cheapskates, The; Lickety Split; Martin, Lauren; Post Toasties; Otterpops, The; Plan B; Cadiere, Catherine; Backlash Trash; Shea'la; Flirttarts, The; Pino Pino; Hateplate (Box 10)
    - Panties, 1996-06; TR-15944 (Box 10)
    - Panties, 1996-06; TR-15945 (Box 10)
    - Erotic Drama, Undated; TR-15946; Panty Raid (Box 10)
    - Positively Phranc, 1991; TR-15947; Phranc; Island Records (Box 10)
      422-848 282-4
    - Static Storm (Original Soundtrack Recording), 1998; TR-15948; Red Eye; Decomposition (Box 10)
      DE05
    - Total Tiger Beat, 1998; TR-15949; Skinned Teen; Spazoom (Box 10)
      Cardiff, United Kingdom
    - Style!, 1998; TR-15950; Sub-Debs (Box 10)
    - A Wonderful Treat, 1991; TR-15951; Suture; I Scream Truck; Bratmobile; Spray-Painted Love; Wondertwins (Box 10)
    - Tattle Tale, 1993-12; TR-15952; Kill Rock Stars (Box 10)
      KRS 301
    - This is a Tracy + The Plastics, 2000-02; TR-15953; Tracy + The Plastics (Box 10)
    - Preview Mixes, 1995; TR-15954; Transisters (Box 10)
    - By the Time We Get to Colorado, 1993; TR-15955; Tribe 8; Outpunk (Box 10)
      OUT 7CA
    - Bunch of Fuckin' Feminists Vol. 2, 1996; TR-15956; Women of Note; Jane Doe; Sta-Prest; S.H.A.G.; Team Dresch; Hussy Snax; Tribe 8; Claudia's Cage; Gamble, Lisa; Dorothea; Deathcard 13; Slow Club; Louder Scully (Box 10)
      Quebec, Canada
  - Video, 1994
    - Getting Close to Nothing, 1994; V-9986; Blood Sausage; Huggy Bear; Mambo Taxi; Cornershop; Bikini Kill; Sister George; Voodoo Queens; BGF (Box 10)
      BGFV001